Raiders!: The Story of the Greatest Fan Film Ever Made is a
documentary film directed by Jeremy Coon.
In 1982, three 11 year-olds in Mississippi set out to remake
their favorite film: Raiders of the Lost Ark.
It took seven turbulent years that tested the limits of their
friendship and nearly burned down their mother's house.
By the end, they had completed every scene except one...
the explosive airplane scene.
30 years later, they attempt to finally realize their childhood dream by building a replica of the 75
foot "Flying Wing" plane from Raiders in a mud pit in the backwoods of Mississippi...
and then blow it up!
This is the story behind the making of what is known
as "the greatest fan film ever made."
Self, played by John Rhys-Davies.
Self, played by Eli Roth.
Self, played by Eric Zala.
Self, played by Chris Strompolos.
Self, played by Jayson Lamb.
Self, played by Kurt Zala.
Raiders!: The Story of the Greatest Fan Film Ever Made is a 2015 American
documentary film directed by Jeremy Coon and Tim Skousen.
The film follows three childhood friends, Eric Zala, Chris Strompolos, and Jayson Lamb, from
1982 to 1989 as they set out to make a fan film of Raiders of the Lost Ark.
35 years later in 2014, it shows how they get back together to finish filming the
"plane sequence", a previously missing scene from their remake.
The film explores themes of pop culture, fan
culture, filmmaking, fan film, fandom.